marketmetweet.com 2012-05-04

# Privacy Policy

Pie Dog Media, LTD (“MarketMeSuite, “ScheduleDroid,” “BlogMe”) takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting the MarketMeSuite website located at www.MarketMeSuite.com and any linked pages, features, content, or application services offered from time to time by MarketMeSuite in connection therewith (the “Site”) and using MarketMeSuite services (the “Services”), you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy.

 _WE DO NOT store financial details (credit card or any other payment information.)_

 **What Does This Privacy Policy Cover?**

This Privacy Policy covers MarketMeSuite’s treatment of personal information that MarketMeSuite gathers when you are on the Site and when you use the Services. This policy also covers MarketMeSuite’s treatment of any personal information that MarketMeSuite’s business partners share with MarketMeSuite.  
This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that MarketMeSuite does not own or control, including but not limited to third party services you access through MarketMeSuite, or to individuals that MarketMeSuite does not employ or manage.

 **What Personal Information About Users Does MarketMeSuite Collect?**

We collect the following types of information from our users:

 **Information You Provide to Us**

We receive and store any information you enter on the Site or through the Services or provide to us in any other way. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of the features of our Site and Services. The personal information you provide may be used for such purposes as responding to your requests for certain services, customizing the content you see, and communicating with you about specials and new products. In order for you to take full advantage of our Site and Services, you must provide registration information, including an e-mail address, password and, in certain circumstances, registration information for the third party services you access through MarketMeSuite. We may also request demographic information and unique identifiers in order to provide you with a more personalized service, but this information is optional. To the extent you provide MarketMeSuite with personal information, you are not anonymous to us.

 _We do NOT store any credit card or payment information._

 **Automatic Information**

We may receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. MarketMeSuite may automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, MarketMeSuite cookie information, and the information you request. MarketMeSuite may use this traffic data to help diagnose problems with its server, analyze trends and administer the Site and Services. Our service may automatically collect usage information, such as the numbers and frequency of visitors to our Site and Services and their components. MarketMeSuite may use this data in aggregate form, that is, as a statistical measure, but not in a manner that would identify you personally. This type of aggregate data may enable us to figure out how often customers use parts of the Site and Services, so we can make the Site and Services appealing to as many users as possible. As part of this use of information, we may provide aggregate information, not information about you personally, to our partners about how our users, collectively, use our Site and Services. If we share this type of statistical data, we do it so that our partners can understand how often people use their areas of our Site and Service, so that they, too, may provide you with optimal MarketMeSuite service.

 **E-mail Communications**

We may receive a confirmation when you open an e-mail from MarketMeTwet if your computer supports this type of program, in order to help us make e-mails more interesting and helpful. We may also send out e-mails with news or promotions. If you do not want to receive promotional e-mail from us, please contact us at hello@MarketMeSuite.com or unsubscribe on any email footer you receive.  
Information From Other Sources  
For purposes such as improving personalization of our service, we may receive information about you from other sources. Like the information you provide to us, we do not share this information with anyone except authorized third parties in connection with providing you with our Services.

 **What about Cookies?**

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we may transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our Site are visited and by how many people. To the extent MarketMeSuite uses cookies, such cookies do not collect personal information, and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personal information to tell us who you are or what your username or e-mail address is; we use cookies to enhance users’ experiences, to learn more about their use of the Site and Services and to improve quality. Most browsers have an option for turning off the cookie feature, which will prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies, as well as (depending on the sophistication of your browser software) allowing you to decide on acceptance of each new cookie in a variety of ways. We strongly recommend that you leave the cookies activated, however, because deleting cookies may reduce the functionality of MarketMeSuite. Ads may appear on the Site or the Services, and advertisers may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by MarketMeSuite and does not cover the use of cookies, if any, by advertisers.

Will MarketMeSuite Share Any of the Information it Receives?  
We neither rent nor sell your personal information to anyone. We share your personal information only as described below.  
Affiliated Business We Do Not Control  
In certain situations, MarketMeSuite may provide services, or sell products jointly with affiliated businesses. We will share customer information that is related to such transactions with that affiliated business. We require our affiliates to provide the same level of privacy protection that we do and they do not have the right to share or use personal information for any purpose other than for an authorized transaction.

 **Agents**

We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you. Examples include removing repetitive information from user lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, and providing customer service. Our agents subscribe to the same level of privacy protection as we do. Unless we tell you differently, MarketMeSuite’s agents do not have any right to use the personal information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us.  
Information You Post  
When you post a message through MarketMeSuite, information about you, including user profile information, may be visible to other users. If you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, that information becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others and redistributed through the internet and other media channels. You may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.

 **Promotional Offers**

We may send offers to certain users on behalf of other businesses. However, when we do so, we do not give the other business your name and address. If you do not wish to receive these offers, please e-mail us at hello@MarketMeSuite.com.  
Business Transfers  
In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Moreover, if MarketMeSuite, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that MarketMeSuite goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, customer information would be one of the assets that is transferred to or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of MarketMeSuite may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

 **Protection of MarketMeSuite and Others**

We may release personal information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with the law; enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of MarketMeSuite, our employees, our users, or others. MarketMeSuite may disclose personal information to parties in compliance with MarketMeSuite’s Copyright Policy, as MarketMeSuite in its sole discretion believes necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, piracy, or other unlawful activity. In such events, MarketMeSuite may disclose name, street address, city, state, zip code, country, phone number, and e-mail address.

 **With Your Consent**

Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your personal information may be shared with third parties, and you will be able to prevent the sharing of this information.

 **Is Information About Me Secure?**

Information you provide to MarketMeSuite related to third party services you access through the Services is protected by the privacy policies and procedures of such third party services. You need to work to protect against unauthorized access to your passwords for those services and to your computer by signing off once you have finished using a shared computer. [We use industry-standard Secure Socket Layer (SSL) software to protect the security of your personal information during transmission, which encrypts all of the information you input.] Only employees who need personal information to perform a specific job (for example, a customer service representative) are granted access to it. All of our employees are kept up to date on our privacy and security practices.

 **What Information Can I Access?**

MarketMeSuite may allow you to access the following information about you for the singular purpose of viewing, and in certain situations, updating that information.  
You may be able to add or update certain information via the Site or Services. When you update information, however, we often maintain a copy of the unrevised information in our records.  
You may delete the MarketMeSuite software from your computer if you wish to cease using MarketMeSuite Services. Please note that information may remain in our records after deletion of such software.  
To the extent your e-mail address is provided to MarketMeSuite, you may receive e-mail or other communications from us. Please note that if you do not want to receive legal notices from us, such as this Privacy Policy, those legal notices will still govern your use of the Site and Services, and you are responsible for reviewing such legal notices for changes.  
As stated previously, you can always opt not to disclose information, even though it may be needed to take advantage of certain MarketMeSuite features.

 **Can Children Use MarketMeSuite’s Services?**

MarketMeSuite is not intended for children. If you are under 18, you may use the Site and Services only with involvement of a parent or guardian.

 **Third Party Sites**

The Site and Services may permit you to access or link to third party websites and information on the Internet, and other websites may contain links to the Site. These other websites and services are not under MarketMeSuite’s control. The privacy and security practices of websites accessed from the Site are not covered by this Privacy Policy, and MarketMeSuite is not responsible for the privacy or security practices or the content of such websites, including but not limited to the third party services you access through MarketMeSuite.

 **Changes to this Privacy Policy**

MarketMeSuite may amend this Privacy Policy. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes to our privacy policy, we will notify you by posting an announcement on our development blog or site so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances if any, it is disclosed.

 **Questions or Concerns**

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy at MarketMeSuite, please send us a detailed message to hello@MarketMeSuite.com or to PieDog Media, LTD, Sussex Road Business Centre,  Gorelston, Norfolk, NR316PF, United Kingdom. 020 3239 4690
